

darren.r.angle@gmail.com 910-539-2453 https://darren.computer References upon request.

HIGHLIGHTS

LLM CRAFT LEADER AT SHOPIFY

Technical Lead / Advisor to nearly all of Shopify's LLM projects. Vectorized and built chat experiences on Shopify's total internal knowledge across 40+ teams. Shipped LLM Help Center saving \$5M/mo.

NeurIPS '23 CONFERENCE PAPER

Identifying Neglected Hypotheses In Neurodegenerative Disease with Large Language Models. Primary technical author. GenBio Workshop. Commissioned by Genentech.

ENGINEERING LEADERSHIP

12+ years of engineering and compassionate management in biotech, healthcare, and advertising.

SEEKING

Engineering and leadership roles working with language models and building out distributed systems at scale.

EDUCATION

BROWN UNIVERSITY MFA Literary Arts, Poetry

with Entertainy Air to, it octing

MACALESTER COLLEGE

BA English, Creative Writing

SKILLS

- Full Stack Software Engineering
- Distributed Systems Design
- Engineering Management
- LLM Fine-tuning, Deployment, and Evaluation in Production
- GPT4, Claude, Open LLMs
- Data Engineering / Pipeline Infra
- Vector DBs, Retrieval Augmented Generation, Agents
- FE: React, Typescript, Remix
- BE: Node, Rails, NoSQL & SQL DBs, k8s, BigQuery, Kafka
- ML: Python, Pytorch, Huggingface
- Clouds: Google, AWS, Azure

RECENT EXPERIENCE

PRISM BIO, HEAD OF AI, 2023 - PRESENT

Built Generative AI capabilities from scratch across Prism's top pharma clients. JnJ: generative data analysis, literature synthesis, RAG, and multi-agent orchestration for drug target discovery. Genentech: LLMs for neglected hypotheses in Alzheimer's (NeurIPS '23) and transformers for competitor innovation prediction. AstraZeneca: Automated trial reports and data visualization. Trusted advisor to multiple innovation teams in life science orgs.

SHOPIFY, LLM CRAFT LEADER, ENGINEERING MGMT, 2022-23

Accelerated career path: senior engineer ⇒ manager ⇒ LLM Craft Leader in 1 year. Guided LLM adoption and best practices across multiple teams and projects, often working directly with CEO and vendor partners (OpenAI, Google, etc). Managed 8 direct reports.

DINA, LEAD ENGINEER, 2021 - 2022

Lead engineer with org-wide impact in business strategy, systems design, and roadmap development. Built multiple web and native applications to facilitate at-home care coordination for patients. Led electronic medical record integrations for multiple hospital systems.

CASECHECK, LEAD ENGINEER / MANAGER, 2018 - 2021

IC and Engineering manager shipping full stack web and native applications directly into hospitals for use before, during and after surgery. Led integration with electronic health records at multiple hospital systems, and migrations to private VPCs for each. Managed 5 direct reports.